Inaban, I believed in you...
Hell yeah!
Even for Inaba-chan, taking care of this much work is impossible!
So, Iori-chan,
you're treating me to that fruit-flavoured milk later on.
Yay!
I get fruit milk!
I'm surprised that they made a bet since it was their fault that Inaba's behind in her work.
I won!
It doesn't matter, as per the usual,
I won so elegantly!
I really can do just anything if I want to!
he'll soon be in for some heavy punishment.
I won! I won!
Shut up over there!
Besides, you got me into this because of that mess of an article you turned in!
Thanks to you, I have to bring the work home with me!
Yes, you're exactly right.
That's why you're turning the fruit milk over to me.
This has nothing to do with that...
Huh?
I got it!
Aoki really went overboard with his report this time.
He went completely along with his interests to write about lunch recommendations for girls,
and it's so obvious that he wrote it based on the food I like.
Isn't that right?
The article that I wrote, "Wrestling Technique Debate: Ropework and Camera Work", is obviously superior.
I picked the wrong person to talk to.
It hurts me if you say that out to me so blankly in real life.
Hurry up and get ready to leave!
We'll take care of the rest once we go!
Yes!
Three weeks have passed since the whole personality switching thing ended.
Nagase made a full recovery from her injuries,
and now we're busy making up for lost time on the next issue of the CRC News.
Three weeks ago, I confessed my feelings to Nagase,
and she acknowledged them.
But with her injuries and the next issue on our minds,
we haven't had a chance to talk about it.
So, the Yamaboshi High School Cultural Research Club is back to life as usual.
Or so we thought...
until school ended the next day.
You're already here?
You're fast, Inaba.
I wasn't able to get it done at home.
I'm definitely finishing this thing today.
Think Yui and Aoki'll be long?
They need to clarify a few things.
I ran into them on the way up.
They're both on clean-up duty today, so they'll be late.
Doesn't having to wait on people seriously piss you off?
It's not like it's their fault, but still...
Well, you can't really complain if it's not their fault.
Makes you want to take out your anger on the nearest freak, huh?
No, it doesn't.
What good would that do?
Taking it out on someone else relieves stress.
Now that's just mean.
I find that making you voice needless observations with a bit of a dark spin to them
is a great way of relieving stress.
What?
You're relieving your stress by taking it out on me, but without making me feel bad?
What's wrong, Inaba?
Inaba?
H-Hold on. What's wrong?
Does your back itch or something?
Hey!
Hey, wait!
What are you doing?!
Come on. Take your clothes off.
Take my clothes off?
Why?
We can't do it if you don't take them off.
Can't do what?
Oh, I know what you're up to!
You're taking your stress out on me, right?
I-Inaba—
What in the world are you doing?!
Get off!
Get off! Get off!
Wait! It's not what it looks like!
I don't know what it is either, but—
Inaba?
Would you mind...
explaining yourselves right now?!
Yui?
What's gotten into you?
Blood?
Did I... do this?
Why?
Hey, every—
The table!
What happened?
Why is it broken?
Hey, Yui, you're bleeding!
Let me see.
Iori!
What's wrong? Did it hurt?
Sorry.
I'm going home.
What happened to them?
That was weird.
Is this really okay?
Onii-chan, going out?
Did something happen?
Was I...
about to go outside?
Why are you asking me?
Sorry, phone call.
Hello?
Nagase?
Taichi, tell me!
Are we—
Um...
Er... Huh?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Good...
evening.
Good... evening?
Sorry!
I don't know why, but before I knew it, I called you.
I felt like I just had to talk to you.
A-Actually, I suddenly wanted to see you, too.
My body just started acting on its own.
You, too?
What's going on?
This is kind of weird.
I'm curious, too.
Hey, you felt like you had to talk to me, right?
Why was that?
What about you?
You wanted to talk to me, right?
I...
That confession at the hospital—
We haven't had a chance to talk—
Have your feelings...
Have your feelings changed since then?
They haven't.
My feelings haven't changed a bit since then.
Okay.
Um...
Same here.
You know, I'm feeling really embarrassed right now.
I'm... feeling it, too.
L-Let's leave it at this for today!
Yeah, let's do that!
O-Okay.
We'll do that.
Sorry to bother you like this.
Bye!
Wait, Nagase—
Your girlfriend?
Sh-She's not my girlfriend!
You're blushing!
But that's a relief.
You were acting so weird a few weeks ago.
You were acting the same way just now, too.
I get it now.
You're lovesick.
I'm not!
Well, it might be better if you thought that, but...
Onii-chan, you're so cute.
Wait, where'd you learn about being lovesick?
Onii-chan needs to have a nice, long talk with you!
I-Inaba?!
Yester—
U-Um...
Bad news.
Yui and Aoki were taken into custody.
Huh?
What?
I don't know the details, but it's being discussed in the faculty room.
I tried calling them, but they aren't answering.
They might be at the station.
Hold on.
What the heck?
Why'd they get taken into custody?
Like I'd know.
Dammit!
Does anyone here know what happened?
You called?
Huh?
Fujishima?
Um...
I don't think anyone called for you.
If you know something, tell us!
Bossing someone around when you're asking for their help, Inaba-san?
Please tell us, Fujishima-san.
Let's see.
If you let me borrow Nagase-san for two hours,
I'll think about it.
I'm not asking for much.
I'm sure Nagase-san will enjoy it, too.
Hey, Fujishima, that's dirty.
Don't touch her!
Again?
Hey. What do you think you're doing?
What are you doing, Yaegashi-kun?
Practicing a dance?
Not really...
Okay.
If you'll tell us what happened to Aoki and Yui,
then two or three hours is nothing!
So tell us, Fujishima-san!
I was just kidding.
I still would've told you even if you didn't take my offer.
Are you serious?!
My determination!
I mean, you three look horrible.
I was just trying to lighten the mood with some humor.
I didn't think you'd hate it that much.
This morning, some boys from Akitaka High started hitting on a few girls from our school.
Kiriyama-san happened to be there and beat the boys to a pulp.
But it looks like she went a bit too far.
The police decided to question her at the station.
And then Aoki-kun came out of the crowd, shouting,
"Where are you taking her?
Let go of her!"
It turned into quite the struggle.
Well, they were just trying to help out their fellow schoolmates.
They'll probably just let them off with a stern warning.
You bet they will.
If they even think of punishing them,
I'll use every trick in the book to stop them.
How do you know so much about this, Fujishima-san?
My dad just happens to be pretty high up in the police department.
That's all.
Oh, how very nice.
You'll make for a very useful connection.
It will cost you, but I'll keep it cheap, just for you.
They're getting along like a house on fire...
Scariest tag team ever...
So Kiriyama and Aoki never showed up today.
Hey, there's something that's been bothering me.
Kiriyama beat up boys from another school, right?
Isn't she...
That's been bothering me, too.
Yui's afraid of men.
She's gotten a lot better recently,
but not to the extent where she can fight men.
But...
You were acting weird this morning, too.
Yeah.
Did you hear a voice in your head when that happened?
Wait, did you hear one, too?
Both of you heard one, too?
Hello. Long time no see.
Well, it hasn't really been that long.
I wonder.
Balloon Vine?!
Yes.
As of yesterday, you will be hearing voices in your heads every so often.
When that happens, your bodies will act on impulse.
Will you cut this shit out?!
We are not guinea pigs!
Oh, right. I haven't apologized to Nagase-san.
I'm very sorry from around the middle of my heart.
Why not leave us alone if you really feel sorry?
Please.
I've told you several times.
You're all just a little too interesting.
Now I'd like to explain what's happening this time.
Simply put, I'm unleashing the desires you hold in your hearts.
Unleashing our desires?
Like I've said before, it'll end when you show me something rather interesting.
You could say that I'm helping
you find your true selves.
"True selves"...
I have a question.
Is being a shut-in against the rules?
I see.
You're very good at analyzing these situations.
My answer is, that can be interesting in itself,
and if it's not, I'll make it interesting.
That's all I can say.
You'll make it interesting?
Maybe I've told you more than I needed to.
Well, until next time.
What's this?
Seriously, what is this?
Do you two have any strategies for avoiding this phenomenon?
I guess not.
We managed to get through last time.
Let's just believe in ourselves and we'll
manage to make it through this time as well.
No, rather, we can do something to make it through.
I'm not looking at this optimistically at all.
You would've been so cool had you laid that out better.
It's impossible.
He's not just incompetent, but an idiot too.
Don't laugh at me.
But yeah,
right now, we can only hope that we can somehow manage.
So it's Balloon Vine again?
Sorry to make you worry about me.
No need to apologize.
We weren't worried about you in the first place.
That's so mean!
Inaba-chan, you're so mean!
But it's great that they let you off with a warning.
Yeah.
I'm totally okay, but...
Kiriyama's absent again?
Yui wanted to save those girls,
even if it meant hitting those boys.
Aoki wanted to stop them from taking Yui away,
even if it meant fighting the police.
Your super-ego would usually stop you from doing something so stupid.
But now...
Your desires get unleashed, and you just can't help yourself.
That's probably why Yui smashed the table two days ago.
Speaking of which, you got on top of me—
Don't you dare talk about that!
Have you no decency?!
You don't bring up bodies people bury!
Maybe I should knock you around until you forget!
Um...
What are you talking about?
Now look what you've done!
You idiot! Dumbass! Retard!
S-Sorry...
It's nothing important.
Before you came in two days ago, my desires got unleashed,
and I... well...
got on top of Taichi.
Oh?
When I wasn't here?
Don't get me wrong!
I just happened to come across a dirty picture right before.
I-I don't know how far I was going to take it,
but I know I wasn't going to cross any lines!
I think.
I've never done it before, anyway.
Back to the issue at hand!
We could manage personality switching just by being careful,
but it won't work for this "desire unleashing" thing.
Yui and Aoki have already caused trouble for other people.
Yeah, there's a risk of involving outsiders this time.
I see two possible ways of dealing with this.
The first is to keep yourself from experiencing any extreme emotions.
The second is to do everything you want without restraint,
living more freely and having more fun than you usually would.
What do you mean?
In other words, we can either empty our minds
so we don't have any desires that might cause a problem,
or we can do the opposite and keep stress from building
by doing whatever we want every so often.
Both sound pretty hard to do.
You're amazing, Inaban!
You already came up with a plan!
Flattery won't get you anywhere.
We'll need to help each other out, too.
Oh... That could work, too.
Was it a bad idea?
No, not really.
Helping each other out isn't a bad idea.
We'll have to see what actually happens for anything else.
We'll deal with the situations case-by-case.
That's all we can do for now.
Yui'll probably be back in school tomorrow.
We can talk more about it then.
Yeah.
We may not know what we need to do,
but I'm sure it'll all work out if we put our heads together!
Yeah!
I know it!
We're counting on you, Taichi.
Take care of Iori.
Sure.
But I can't just take care of Nagase. I'll take—
Iori is the only person you need to worry about.
And Aoki can take care of Yui—
Wait, we can't really count on you.
Don't underestimate me.
You'll be in for a surprise.
Wait, Inaban, aren't you coming?
I still have to work on our newspaper.
I want to get some more stuff done.
We can stay and help out.
You don't need to!
Come on, hurry up! Get out!
I can't work if you're here!
See you.
Did I do it right?
Are they going to be okay?
What should I do?
Taichi, do you have a moment?
Yeah.
You don't usually call this late.
Sorry, but I have to tell you something.
We didn't really get to finish last time.
O-Oh, right.
That...
It might not really be a good time to talk about it,
but I think it's really important, so...
Can we keep things the way they are?
The way they are?
It sounds pretty bad to ask that of you,
but I want to keep our distance right now.
We're kind of in a weird situation with this whole "desire unleashing" thing, right?
Yeah.
I don't think it's a good idea to move forward with our relationship in this kind of situation.
You're right.
Sorry.
I wasn't thinking about that at all.
We're probably really dangerous right now.
We're really dangerous,
no matter how you look at it.
We don't know what we might do.
Oh, could I make a confession of my own?
A confession?
Well, I still really don't know much about myself.
Sometimes, I wonder if it's really okay for me to be like this.
So I'm actually a little excited about this desire unleashing.
Excited?
The desires in our hearts are going to be unleashed.
I get the feeling I might find out more about who I really am.
That's why I'm excited.
I hate myself for thinking things like that,
but I can't stop.
Okay, confession time over!
Thanks for listening!
I'll treat you to a snack or something tomorrow.
That's another part of who you are.
What?
I mean, looking at yourself objectively like that is part of who you are.
I think you can see your true self in how you live your life.
Whenever I'm with you, I feel like everything's going to be all right.
See you.
Yeah, see you.
It'll work out.
I'll make it work out.
This time...
I have to do it right.
She's strong! She's super cute!
Yahoo!
She's cute! She's cheerful!
No! Don't look!
No! No!
Her hair's pretty!
She's tiny! She's pure!
Sorry I'm that kind of person.
I made a huge mistake!
You think I'd know?!
Don't ask me!
You've let me down, Inaba.
I never thought you'd turn your back on a friend.